嗯，你好，美好的一天。
Well, hello, good day.
Bueno, hola, buen día.
当他调整椅子时，我趁机……
While he adjusts the chair, I take the opportunity to...
Mientras acomoda la silla aprovecho para...
首先要感谢每一位走到我面前的人对我说的话。
to thank above all the words that each of those who went up to me dedicated to me.
para agradecer sobre todo las palabras que me dedicaron cada uno de los que subieron a
走上舞台，感谢马卡报的认可、这个奖项。
to the stage, thank Marca for this recognition, this award.
al escenario, agradecer a Marca por este reconocimiento, este premio.
好吧，我们的关系已经很多年了，感谢上帝，我们已经见过几次面了。
Well, we have a relationship for years because thank God we have seen each other several times.
Bueno, tenemos una relación de hace años porque gracias a Dios nos hemos visto varias veces.
我们做了几次采访
we have done several interviews
hemos hecho varias entrevistas
正如我刚才所说，他们非常善于选择阿根廷人和加泰罗尼亚人。
As I just said, they were very good in choosing an Argentinian and also a Catalan.
Como decía recién, estuvieron muy bien al elegir un argentino y también un catalán.
它们是我的两栋房子，两件事......
They are my two houses, the two things that...
son mi dos casas, las dos cosas que...
这代表了我，我们是一个幸福的家庭......
that represent me, where we were a happy family with...
que me representan, donde fuimos familia feliz junto a...
致我的家人，我们和我的家人在一起很幸福，今天不是去一个地方的时候
to my family, where we are happy with my family and today it is not time to be in a place that
a mi familia, donde somos felices junto a mi familia y hoy no toca estar en un lugar que
我们也很高兴，我们真的很喜欢这座城市、俱乐部和新朋友。
that we are also very happy, that we are really enjoying the city, the club, and the new people.
que también somos muy felices, que estamos disfrutando muchísimo de la ciudad, del club, de la gente nueva que es.
我们知道，我们人生的新阶段。
that we know, a new stage of our life.
que conocemos, una etapa nueva de nuestra vida.
并很享受它，但没什么，我只是想感谢什么......
and enjoying it a lot, but nothing, I just wanted to thank what...
y disfrutándola muchísimo, pero nada, solo quería agradecer lo que...
他们说的是在不认识我的情况下...
What they said is that without knowing me...
Lo que dijeron es que sin conocerme...
每个人都非常成功，所以非常感谢你们，也非常感谢你们来到这里。
Everyone was very successful, so thank you very much and thank you very much for being here too.
Estuvieron muy acertados todos, así que muchas gracias y muchas gracias por estar acá también.